Here's the solution. In the utility class, we add the
helper methods that were provide in the gist. We also
declared these strings in the strings.xml file. In the Forecast
Adapter Class, in the bind view method, we finish off the
remaining to do's. After we read the high temperature value
from the cursor, we go and try to find the
text view, represented by the ID, list item high text
view. Then we use a utility function to format the temperature
so that it can be displayed in the text view. Then we do the
same for the low temperature value. In the forecast fragment class, in the on
create view method, we remove the use of the simple cursor adapter. Instead, we
use the new forecast adapter and then we set it on the list view.